Guide to the Cornell University Office of the Dean of Women records, 1922-1953.
Cornell University Office of the Dean of Women records, 1922-1953
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Office of the Dean of Women records, 1922-1953.
37-2-260
Cornell University. Office of the Dean of Women.
4 cubic ft.
Correspondence and subject files.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence and subject files of the Dean of Women.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence and subject files of the Dean of Women.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Administration.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to the permission of the office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- Board of Trustees, 1930-1942 (Box 1)
- Cornell Women's Clubs, 1927-1940 (Box 1)
- Colleges... Home Economics, 1943 (Box 1)
- Cornell Day for Women, 1942 (Box 1)
- Cornell Women's Clubs, 1938-1939 (Box 1)
- Loans Granted, 1950-1951 (Box 1)
- Loans Granted, 1951-1952 (Box 1)
- Loans Granted, 1952-1953 (Box 1)
- Housing Cooperatives, 1939-1942 (Box 1)
- Housing...Correspondence with Res. Halls, 1943-1944 (Box 1)
- Residential Halls, 1943-1944 (Box 1)
- Balch Halls, 1929 (Box 1)
- Balch Halls, 1929-1930 (Box 1)
- Sage Hall Housing, 1939-1941 (Box 1)
- Dean of Women - Annual Reports, 1929 (Box 1)
- Counselors of Students, 1940-1942 (Box 1)
- Comptroller and Treasurer, 1940-1942 (Box 1)
- University Proctor, 1932-1938 (Box 1)
- Women's Self-Govt. Policy, 1923-1946 (Box 1)
- Women's Self-Govt. Documents (Box 1)
- Cosmopolitan Club (Box 1)
- Alumnae Scholarships, 1937-1942 (Box 1)
- Cornell Day, 1940 (Box 1)
- Cornell Women's Clubs Federation, 1929-1939 (Box 1)
- A.A.U.W. (Amer Assoc of Univ Women), 1926-1935 (Box 1)
- Institute of Women's Professional Relations, 1939-1942 (Box 1)
- Association to Aid Scientific Research for Women, 1922-1928 (Box 1)
- Cosmopolitan Club, 1939-1940 (Box 1)
- Cornell United Religious Work, 1934-1942 (Box 1)
- Cornell United Religious Work, Freshman Camp (Women), 1940-1942 (Box 1)
- National Association of Deans of Women, 1935-1938 (Box 1)
- Miss Fitch - Personal speaking engagements; letters from former CU students; one letter from Mary Donlon, (11-23-1934), 1935-1937 (Box 1)
- Deans, Other Guidance Personnel Correspondence 1944 (Box 1)
- Deans of Women, 1940-1942 (Box 1)
- Sturtevant, Sarah, 1931-1940 (Box 1)
- Statistics for Housing Committee, 1920 (Box 1)
- Housing for Colored Women Students (infor on rooming or apts. downtown houses), 1939-1940 (Box 1)
- Risley Hall, 1929-1935 (Box 1)
- Miss Nye - Personal (mainly letters written by Miss Fitch after Miss Nye became ill), 1935 (Box 1)
- Housing plans of Dorms, 1921 (Box 1)
- Housing --Correspondence with Res Hall, 1944-1946 (Box 1)
- President, 1941-1942 (Box 1)
- Dean: University Faculty Administration, 1941-1942 (Box 1)
- Deans of Women, 1927-1939 (Box 1)
- Counselor of Students, 1943 (Box 1)
- Reports of the Dean of Women, 1940-1942 (Box 1)
- Employment Reports, 1932-1938 (Box 2)
- Employment, 1941-1942 (Box 2)
- N.Y.A., 1940-1942 (Box 2)
- Employment Reports, 1941-1945 (Box 2)
- N.Y.A., 1935-1936 (Box 2)
- The Cornell Women's News, 1925 (Box 2)
- Vouchers, 1928-1936 (Box 2)
- Vouchers, 1927-1938 (Box 2)
- Telephone and Telegraph, 1942-1944 (Box 2)
- Finances... General, 1943-1945 (Box 2)
- Folder has no title, but seems to concern expenses in general, 1916-1919 (Box 2)
- Finances - requisitions, 1941-1943 (Box 2)
- Requisitions, 1937-1938 (Box 2)
- Requisitions, 1938-1939 (Box 2)
- Requisitions, 1941-1942 (Box 2)
- Finance- Vouchers, 1943-1945 (Box 2)
- Requisitions, 1935-1940 (Box 2)
- Requisitions, 1939-1940 (Box 2)
- Requisitions, 1943-1944 (Box 2)
- Finance - Requisitions, 1942-1945 (Box 2)
- Faculty, 1930-1933 (Box 2)
- Medical Dept. Dr Young's Nutrition Project, 1943-1944 (Box 2)
- Medical Dept., 1941 (Box 2)
- Medical Dept., 1931-1938 (Box 2)
- Omicron Nu, 1922 (Box 2)
- Placement Office, 1942 (Box 2)
- University Placement Bureau, 1932-1939 (Box 2)
- Furniture for #1 Sage Ave. Miss Brummett, 1941-1942 (Box 2)
- Women Students Loan Fund, 1935-1936 (Box 2)
- Women's Glee Club Fund, 1935-1936 (Box 2)
- Women Students Loan Fund, 1936-1937 (Box 2)
- Women Students Loan Fund, 1937-1938 (Box 2)
- Women Students Loan Fund, 1938-1939 (Box 2)
- Women Students Loan Fund, 1939-1940 (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous Loans, 1936-1937 (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous Loans, 1937-1939 (Box 2)
- Loans, 1922-1933 (Box 2)
- Loans, 1931-1934 (Box 2)
- Leopold Schepp Foundation, 1929-1940 (Box 2)
- Loans Granted, 1948-1949 (Box 2)
- Loans Granted, 1949-1950 (Box 2)
- Loan Payments, 1939-1941 (Box 2)
- Loan Correspondence, 1939-1941 (Box 2)
- Alumnae Loan Fund, 1936-1937 (Box 2)
- Alumnae Loan Fund, 1937-1938 (Box 2)
- Alumnae Loan Fund, 1938-1940 (Box 2)
- Grant Fund, 1938-1939 (Box 2)
- Guild Fund, 1938-1939 (Box 2)
- Hunter Loan Fund, 1937-1939 (Box 2)
- Women's Emergency Relief Fund, 1937 (Box 2)
- Women's Glee Club Fund, 1936-1937 (Box 2)
- Women's Self- Govt. Association, 1949-1951 (Box 3)
- Women's Self-Govt. Association Executive Committee Minutes, 1949-1953 (Box 3)
- Executive Committee Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 3)
- Judiciary Committee Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 3)
- Residence Council Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 3)
- House of Representatives, 1951-1952 (Box 3)
- W.S.G.A. House of Representatives - Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 3)
- W.S.G.A. House of Representatives - Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 3)
- Folder without title (contains a few prints) (Box 3)
- W.S.G.A. Executive Committee Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 3)
- W.S.G.A. Executive Committee Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 3)
- Judicianry Committee Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 3)
- W.S.G.A. Judiciary Committee Minutes, 1952-1953 (Box 3)
- Curtiss-Wright Program: ind. list of "cadettes", mainly re: housing in Comstock A&B, 1943 (Box 3)
- W.S.G.A. Policy and Procedure, 1943-1947 (Box 3)
- Student Conduct, 1930-1932 (Box 3)
- Student Conduct, 1935-1939 (Box 3)
- Committee on Student Conduct, 1942-1943 (Box 3)
- Scholarships Awarded, 1951-1952 (Box 3)
- Scholarships Granted, 1952-1953 (Box 3)
- Scholarships Awarded, 1950-1951 (Box 3)
- Scholarships Awarded, 1948-1949 (Box 3)
- Scholarships... Rochester Alliance Scholarship, 1939 (Box 3)
- Scholarships and Fellowships, 1934-1941 (Box 3)
- Scholarships, Grants in Aid, 1940-1941 (Box 3)
- Federation of Women's' Clubs Scholarships, 1942-1943 (Box 3)
- Federation Scholarships Rejects and Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 3)
- Federation, 1945-1946 (Box 3)
- Federation Scholarships, 1944-1945 (Box 3)
- Federation, 1943-1946 (Box 3)
- Scholarships Applications, 1944 (Box 3)
- Fellowships, 1929-1932 (Box 3)
- Scholarships, 1935 (Box 3)
- Scholarship Room Applications, 1940-1941 (Box 3)
- Students Scholarship, 1924-1926 (Box 3)
- Fellowships, 1929-1930 (Box 3)
- Willard Straight Hall, 1938-1946 (Box 3)
- Sororities-General, 1941 (Box 3)
- Panhellenic Sororities, 1940-1941 (Box 3)
- Sororities...Panhellenic, 1942 (Box 3)
- Sororities...Panhellenic, 1943 (Box 3)
- Panhellenic, 1943 (Box 3)
- Sororities, 1927-1930 (Box 3)
- Panhellenic, 1938-1940 (Box 3)
- Women's Self-Govt. Association Judiciary Committee Minutes, 1948-1949 (Box 3)
- Judiciary Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 3)
- Mortar Board, 1927-1940 (Box 3)
- General Correspondence, 1935-1942 (Box 4)
- Summer Session, 1920 (Box 4)
- Summer Session Student Problems and Interviews, 1945 (Box 4)
- Abnormals - Anonymous Letters (Box 4)
- Student Affairs Committee, 1918-1930 (Box 4)
- Student Affairs Committee Correspondence and Memoranda, 1924-1930 (Box 4)
- Student Affairs Committee, 1926-1932 (Box 4)
- Women's Self-Govt Association Residence Council Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 4)
- History and Information on Growth and Development of W.S.G.A. rules, 1933-1946 (Box 4)
- Women's Self-Govt Association Residence Council Minutes, 1952-1953 (Box 4)
- Sorority House Committee Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 4)
- Residence Council Minutes, 1948-1950 (Box 4)
- Women's Self-Govt Association Residence Council Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 4)
- Women's Self-Govt Association Residence Council Minutes, 1948-1949 (Box 4)
- Chairman of Activities Report; Cynthia Foster, 1948-1949 (Box 4)
- Women's Self-Govt Association Executive Committee Minutes, 1948-1949 (Box 4)
- Sorority House Committee Minutes, 1948-1949 (Box 4)
- Women's Self-Govt Association Orientation, 1939-1944 (Box 4)
- Orientation...Materials, 1942-1943 (Box 4)
- Freshmean Orientation, 1946-1947 (Box 4)
- Women's Self-Govt Association Junior Advisory Committee, 1939-1945 (Box 4)
- Women's Self-Govt Association Cottage Presidents, 1942-1944 (Box 4)
- Minutes-Executive Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 4)
- Minutes-House of Representatives, 1947-1948 (Box 4)
- Women's Self-Govt Association Executive Committee Minutes, 1944-1946 (Box 4)
- VP Training Course and Method of Selection, 1943-1944 (Box 4)
- Women's Self-Govt Association, 1942-1945 (Box 4)
- Women's Self-Govt Association General, 1944-1945 (Box 4)
- Orientation, 1942 (Box 4)
- Women's Self-Govt Association Presidents Report, 1945-1946 (Box 4)
- Women's Self-Govt Association Residence Council Minutes, 1945-1946 (Box 4)
- Women's Self-Govt Association House of Representatives, 1944-1947 (Box 4)
- Willard Straight Hall General, 1944-1945 (Box 4)
- Willard Straight, Proposed Additions Committee, 1945 (Box 4)